vzochat.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy Statement / Free Video Chat Conferendo

[conferen.do](http://www.conferendo.com/en/Default.aspx) is a service of TrueConf LLC('TRUECONF').

TRUECONF is committed to protecting your privacy at all times. We do not sell, rent or lease any of the information collected to third parties without your prior permission. This Statement of Privacy governs data collection and usage at all TRUECONF sites and services, including Conferendo.

## Collection of Personal Information

In order to use Conferendo you must first setup an account. During this process TRUECONF collects certain information such as your name, email address and age among others. TRUECONF does not associate any sensitive data, such as your race, religion, sexual orientation or political affiliations with personally identifiable information.However if you directly disclose personally identifiable information through any of the Conferendo affiliated sites or services, this information may be collected for use by others. TRUECONF does not read, eavesdrop or record any of your private online communications. In order to continue to develop a better online experience, TRUECONF collects computer hardware and software information which may include: your browser type, Internet IP address, Operating System and referring Website addresses. Certain Conferendo usage information is also collected by TRUECONF which can include: chat session times, login times and software version numbers.This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain the quality of the service, and to provide aggregate statistics regarding use of the service. This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TRUECONF is not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of third party Web sites.

## Use of your Personal Information

TRUECONF collects and uses your personal information in order to enable you to use the Conferendo Service. TRUECONF also may use personal information to inform you of promotions and specials. Except for information used to send electronic advertisements and promotions, as described above, TRUECONF does not sell, rent or lease any of the information collected to third parties.

TRUECONF will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good belief that such action is necessary to:

  * (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TRUECONF or the site;
  * (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TRUECONF or the site;
  * (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TRUECONF, its sites or services, or the public.

## Cookies

TRUECONF uses 'cookies' to help deliver a convenient, personalized online experience.A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of a cookie is to provide a better online experience. However you have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies if you prefer.

If you choose to decline cookies, you will not be able to use some interactive features within the [Conferendo.com](http://www.conferendo.com/en/Default.aspx).

## Control your Personal Information

TRUECONF offers you a range of choices for the collection and use of your personal information. When you register for an Conferendo ID, you can choose exactly which information you would like to share in your Conferendo Profile which is visible to other users. This can be changed at any later point from the Conferendo Profile page on the Web site.In addition, at this page you can choose to opt to not receive promotional emails from our partners. These procedures are safeguarded to prevent someone else from making choices about the usage and control of your personal information. In each instance you are required to enter your password before submitting the updated information. TRUECONF will periodically inform you via email of new feature announcements, software releases, technical service issues and product surveys. These emails are considered essential to the provision of the service you have requested so you will not be able to unsubscribe from these mailings.

## Security of your Personal Information

TRUECONF secures the personal information you provide on our servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

##  Notification of Changes

TRUECONF will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. When TRUECONF posts changes to this Statement, you will see the term 'Updated' next to the Privacy Policy link on [TRUECONF homepage](http://trueconf.com/).
